

## Madhusudan Panda

Motion Graphic / Graphic Designer

#### **SKILLS**

Creativity
Typography
Technology
Communication

# SOFTWARE

Management

Photoshop

Illustrator

Premiere

After effects

Adobe XD

#### **LANGUAGES**

English
Hindi
Oriya

#### **CONTACT**



madhusudan.panda1@gmail.com



9861616961



Hyderabad, Telangana



#### **ABOUT ME**

Creative graphic designer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. More than **1.5** years of experience developing designs for mobile apps, online websites, video, and advertising. Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs.

#### **EDUCATION**

2010-2012 CHSE,ODISHA
Council of higher secondary education in ( Arts )

2012-2015 SCTE & VT, ODISHA
Diploma in (Mechanical Engineering).

2015-2018 BPUT,ODISHA

Bachelor of Technology in (Mechanical Engineering).

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2018-2019 **NSDC** 

National Skill Development Corporation ( Skill India ) as a Assessor.

2019-present Genii IT Services Pvt. Ltd.

Working as a UX/MotionGraphic/Graphic Designer in Tradin project.

### **HOBBIES**







